What should I do?
I’m worried about Grandma.
Why is my luck so terrible?
This year, you’ll enter a new social circle,
where you’ll inevitably face conflict
because you aren’t accepted.
And earning acceptance there won’t be easy.
You have to learn how to survive
and prove yourself with your abilities.
Oh.
A foreigner will bring trouble into your life.
Ah!
Great, why is your dream so vivid?
Wake up already. Wake up, Great!
Whose body is this?
Stop! Where are you going?
To the toilet.
What’s a toilet, and what do you do there?
To take a dump.
Hey, Gaew.
This Gaew doesn’t seem like the old Gaew.
Come on, strike me!
What are you doing, Gaew?
I want lightning to strike me,
so I can go back to where I came from.
(Bangkok, 2026)
Rich, you have to help him.
No matter what’s wrong with Great,
or how hard it is.
Even if I have to sell my resort,
I’ll do it.
Yes, Grandma.
(Year 1036 of Thai minor era)
Why do you think Gaew did it?
I didn’t do it, P’Sri.
This is my first time meeting Bua.
How could I get her pregnant?
Lies.
I know people like you always lie.
Stop making excuses.
A troublemaker like you
is bound to do something like this.
I’m not surprised you did this to Bua.
Dear.
I’m sorry
for not raising Gaew properly.
I tried to love and raise him
the same way I raised Sri and Dech.
But I don’t know why he can’t be good
and always brings us trouble.
It’s my fault.
The doctor told us that
Bua is already two months pregnant.
If this child is Gaew’s,
then that means
it’s the grandchild of Lord Ramnarong, your friend.
This is ridiculous.
I met Bua for the first time today.
How could I get her pregnant?
Enough with the excuses.
Bua lives here.
What do you mean it's your first meeting?
I’m telling the truth.
Are you talking back?
Mother.
May I ask Bua a few questions?
What else do you need to ask her?
-I’ve already asked everything.
-Please let me.
Jumpa.
Just let Sri ask.
So we’ll get the full story.
Bua.
Let me ask you again.
Who got you pregnant?
-Where are you going?
-Shh.
Answer me.
It was Lord Gaew.
Then tell me.
When did Gaew do that to you?
That’s enough, Sri.
She’s been hurt enough.
Something improper happened in our household.
And Gaew claimed he’s accused.
When both sides are telling different stories,
I can’t let it slide.
I agree with P’Sri, Mother.
Answer me, Bua.
It happened last month.
You said you’re two months pregnant.
So how could it be last month?
And how did you know you’re pregnant?
How did I know?
Why would you ask such a question?
How could a woman not know she’s pregnant?
Just tell him you’ve been feeling dizzy,
having headaches, and feeling unwell.
Yes.
I’ve been dizzy and nauseous,
and feeling unwell.
Then how did you two do it?
Did Gaew force himself on you?
Is that true, Gaew?
Who examined you?
There was no doctor, was there?
Since it’s come to this,
then I’ll examine Bua…
and see if she’s really pregnant.
Are you a doctor?
How can you examine her?
Please let me try.
Bua, give me your hand.
Come on, Bua.
So strange.
If you’re really pregnant,
what are you afraid of?
Are you making excuses now?
What are you going to do with Bua?
Auntie.
What could I possibly do?
She still has her period.
Bua.
You still have your period, haven’t you?
Am I right?
That’s a betel juice stain.
Betel juice stain?
Are you sure?
Bua, this cloth belongs to you, doesn’t it?
Yes.
Why do you still have your period if you’re pregnant?
Hm?
A lie has no legs.
That’s true.
Sri, are you saying I’m lying?
I was talking about Bua.
Not you, mother.
Why are you getting defensive?
I’m not defensive.
I’m perfectly normal.
Let’s do this.
If you refuse to tell the truth,
I’ll hand you over to the authorities for questioning.
And you’ll be whipped until you confess.
I lied.
I’m not pregnant.
I was only following orders.
You’re lying. My lady never ordered you.
But Aunt Prik did.
Prik!
Fine.
I admit it.
I was the one who ordered Prik.
And Prik ordered Bua to do it.
I did all this
to protect our family.
I don’t want Gaew to stay here.
Because he only brings disgrace upon us.
Jumpa.
Even so,
lying is still wrong.
A sin is a sin,
no matter who commits it.
The day before,
Gaew’s already apologized
and promised to turn over a new leaf, didn’t he?
Why do you have to drag up the past
and make up lies?
I understand now.
Mother.
I brought a gift for you.
What is it?
Durian stinks so bad.
Take it away.
I feel you, Dech.
Sri.
You said you brought me a gift,
but this is more like a gift for your father.
You have a point.
-Would you like some, my lady?
-Prik.
Take it away from me.
Take it wherever you want.
I’m serious.
Look at you.
I forgot you two don’t like durian.
But something this good doesn’t come around every day.
Exactly.
I don’t think it smells bad.
It smells really good.
Oh, look at you.
Durian is the king of fruits.
Something this good,
why don’t you enjoy it?
Excuse me.
Gaew.
Thank you so much, P’Sri.
I would’ve ended up being the scapegoat without you.
Don’t say that, Gaew.
I only did the right thing.
The truth always comes out in the end.
Don’t be angry with my mother.
She’s like a fire.
Burns hot at first, but eventually cools down.
Don’t hold it against her.
I didn’t mean to hurt you.
I’m not angry.
I understand her.
I’m just getting a headache.
Gaew.
I’ve been wondering since I came back.
Why do you speak and act differently?
Unlike the old Gaew.
Prik.
Yes?
Tell Juang to throw away those unripe durians.
Get them out of my house right now!
Yes, my lady.
Wait.
Please don’t throw them away.
I’ll take them.
How foolish.
Who eat unripe durian?
What could you possibly do with it?
It’s edible.
I’ll make it so those who can’t stand durian like you two,
can eat it without any problem.
You must be the only person in Ayutthaya
who’s crazy enough to eat it.
How are you going to make unripe durian edible?
I’m curious too.
What secret technique do you have?
Just wait and see.
P’Juang, P’Waen, please carry them to the kitchen.
Yes.
Unripe durian?
Honestly, Sri.
Why did you pick both the ripe and unripe ones?
They told me I could pick,
so I picked the tree clean.
Coming through.
Is this really durian?
Yes.
This is unripe durian fried until crispy.
It doesn’t smell
and can be stored for a long time.
It’s real.
What do you mean, Dech?
Beautiful color.
And it hardly smells.
It looks delicious.
If you want it to taste better,
sprinkle salt on it.
P’Sri, try it.
Even from Lanna to Malacca,
and from Champa to Dawei,
I never tasted anything like this before.
I feel strangely light and dreamy.
Tell me.
This is not a dream, right?
Help.
Someone help me.
I can’t stop eating.
Now I can die in peace.
I’m afraid to swallow,
because I don’t want it to be gone.
Do you feel the same way?
I’m just like you.
I nearly cried swallowing the last bite.
But the flavor still lingers in my mouth.
It tastes heavenly.
Very crunchy,
and so perfectly crisp,
Soft and smooth, a tasty treat,
Every chew makes joy complete,
Durian’s bliss is hard to beat.
Jumpa.
It’s really crispy
like I'm eating an entire durian orchard.
If this is a dream, I never want to wake up.
But if this is real,
why does it feel like I’m ascending to heaven?
Gaew is amazing.
Am I about to reach nirvana?
What is this?
Is this really fried durian?
How did I live without it before?
The flavor is extraordinary.
Fried durian!
Not bad, right, Dech?
Not bad at all, P'Sri.
I’ve changed my mind.
It’s just so-so.
Right, mother?
I agree.
Just don’t make it too often.
Dech.
Where’s Gaew?
He went down to the kitchen, not sure why.
P’Sri.
Hm?
Do you think Gaew has changed?
Yes.
What happened?
There was a misunderstanding,
so I used the Krishna Kali spell
to uncover the truth.
It must be serious
so you resort to that spell.
But in the end,
Gaew hadn’t done anything evil,
so the spell couldn’t harm him.
No wonder.
He’s so strange.
He’s insane.
What’s the Krishna Kali spell, P’Muen?
Uh…
it’s a prayer chant.
You weren’t feeling well before,
so I prayed for you.
What kind of prayer
sends me across centuries?
What did you say?
Nothing.
I was wondering.
Everyone...
keeps saying I’ve changed.
That I’m possessed.
And you.
You said I lost my mind.
Didn’t you?
You speak strangely.
Nothing like a normal person.
I agree with Dech.
Maybe this is you guys' fate.
I just hope it’s a good kind of fate.
I think it’s a bad one.
Maybe a doomed fate.
There, there.
By the way, what did you tell Pin and Yam to fetch?
Crispy catfish salad.
It’s really good with a drink.
Catfish?
Why crispy?
How did you make it?
It’s not that hard.
This is another strange thing.
Gaew never used the kitchen.
Gaew’s spicy salad scents the air,
Crispy catfish so light and rare,
Tangy, fiery, rich delight,
Melts in your mouth till the final bite.
P’Sri.
What got into you?
Try it.
Dip it in the sauce.
It's crunchy and has many layers.
Since when can he cook this good?
Who exactly is this Gaew?
Well?
It’s average.
Oh.
You two brothers
couldn’t be more different.
One is polite,
calm,
kind-hearted,
and quick-witted.
While the other one
is a poser,
strict,
and full of himself.
You’re talking strangely again.
You don’t know me well.
You don’t know me well either, P'Muen.
Lord Gaew really has changed a lot.
He’s become considerate and caring.
Even so,
that doesn’t compare to Lord Muen’s perfection.
He’s handsome,
composed,
and talented.
His reputation spreads throughout Ayutthaya,
admired by many people.
He’s also skilled at swordsmanship
and horseback riding.
When it comes to horse riding, I’m confident.
I even won a gold medal.
But you can’t ride horses, my lord.
I can.
I’ve been riding since I was a kid.
Have you really lost your mind?
Did you forget you fell off a horse
and became terrified of them?
Maybe Gaew really changed.
This new Gaew behaves much better than before.
You should be happy, Dech.
Don’t stay hung up on the old Gaew.
He keeps talking about the past.
And don’t move on.
There.
Another strange word.
What’s moo on?
Move on.
Move on means
leaving one place and going somewhere else.
But if you don’t move on,
you stay stuck in the past, refusing to move forward.
Then I’ll move on first.
You can keep talking.
I’ll get you to your room.
Get up.
Ouch, P’Muen.
You’re so heavy.
Don’t put all your weight on me.
P’Muen, get on the bed.
P’Muen.
Let me go.
Stay here.
Don’t go.
P’Muen?
P’Muen.
Yam.
Wake up.
My lord.
Please don’t ask me to sink lord Muen’s boat.
I’m scared.
You sank his boat?
You sank lord Muen’s boat?
Yam!
-Hey!
What's this?
How would I know?
Ow.
Why’d you kick me?
Why are you in my arms?
You hugged me first,
as if scared I’d disappear.
And now you’re blaming me?
Me? Hugging you?
Yes!
P’Muen
P’Muen!
P’Muen.
What is it?
Where are you going?
Not your business.
Can I come with you?
For what?
I’m bored being at home all day.
I want to go to the city.
Please let me tag along.
Please, P’Muen.
There are other boats. Have Yam take you.
Don’t be so cold.
I just want to tag along.
I promise I won’t cause any trouble.
Please, P’Muen.
Please.
Please let me come.
Pretty please?
Fine.
Suit yourself.
Thank you.
Why are you blocking my way?
Why are you following us?
That’s up to my master.
Are you challenging me?
What challenge?
We’ll see.
Move.
Get out of the way.
P’Muen!
P’Muen.
What’s that?
Wat Phanan Choeng.
You don’t know?
Oh.
Wat Phanan Choeng.
I know it.
It’s breathtakingly beautiful.
I have business with Reung at the police department.
Wait for me here.
Can I borrow your boat?
I want to go to Wat Phanan Choeng.
Okay? I’ll be right back.
Gaew.
-Let’s go, P’Yam.
-Yes, sir.
Gaew!
Gaew.
Yay!
Be careful, Gaew.
Hey.
How are you, my friend?
Excuse me.
My stomach hurts.
I need to excuse myself to take a dump.
Mhm.
Hey.
P’Yam, what’s wrong with the boat?
Ah! My lord!
Hey! Pin!
Hey.
Ah!
Lord Gaew!
My lord.
Lord Muen.
The guy who came with you fell into the water!
Gaew.
My lord.
Gaew!
Lord Muen!
My lord, lord Muen went underwater.
Come on, P’Muen.
P’Muen.
-Lord Muen.
-Pin!
Lord Muen.
Pin!
You sank Lord Gaew’s boat!
Your master tried to sink lord Muen’s boat first.
You!
You wanna punch me?
Stop, P'Pin, P'Yam!
Let's help P’Muen first.
How?
Huh?
P’Muen.
Gaew.
You’re safe now.
Don’t look. Don’t look at his lips.
Ah.
I want to thank you
for saving my life.
I should thank you too.
You jumped in to save me,
even though you’re not a strong swimmer.
I helped because I wanted to.
I also helped because I wanted to.
As for the mouth thing…
I know.
I’ve seen missionaries did it to save people.
It’s called CPR.
CPR.
I hope you don’t think too much about it.
About what, P’Muen?
I was saving a life.
Mhm.
If you’re not bothered …
that’s good.
Look over there.
So many stars tonight.
Where I live…
I mean the city I live in…
has so much light,
so we never see this many stars.
But you’ve lived here.
You’re talking strangely.
Look, P'Muen.
Hm?
That one.
That's the Orion constellation.
Which one?
And that one,
is the Scorpius constellation.
And over there,
the ones that lined up,
is the Gemini constellation.
I never thought
they had names
and shapes too.
They’ve always been there.
We just…
didn’t look up to see them.
The stars…
are beautiful tonight.
Maybe
the spell really makes you lose your mind.
Did I lose my mind?
I wouldn’t call you crazy.
I think you’re…
cuter now?
Annoying, actually.
Aha!
I miss grandma so much.
My lord.
You know what, P’Yam?
Besides markets,
my hometown also has convenience stores.
What’s a convenience store?
Does it sell magical things?
It’s just a normal store
that opens all day and all night.
How’s that possible?
People need sleep.
Are there a hundred servants working?
No.
The staff just work in shifts.
No hundred servants.
Wow.
You can put it here.
Thank you.
Help!
My lord.
Argh!
Officer, over there!
That way.
Here.
Thank you so much.
If it weren’t for you, I’d be in trouble.
Your accent is so good.
I’ve lived here since I was born.
My name is Maria Guyomar.
And you?
Maria Guyomar.
12 Thai Desserts.
By Thao Thong Kip Ma.
Who is that?
What a funny name.
Hey.
Don’t make fun of her.
She was the head of the royal dessert kitchen
for King Narai.
So?
What’s your name?
My name is... Great.
No.
It's Gaew.
Gaew.
Thank you again.
Maria Guyomar.
You can call me Mali.
I’m a new person now.
I apologize for what I did in the past.
Why are we secretly following Lord Gaew?
I’m afraid he’s going to cause trouble.
You can call me Falcon.
What’s happening to me?
Why is my heart racing like this?
Why are you arresting me?
You’re a murder suspect.
Me? A murderer?